We hunted it into extinction... Now it's hunting us.
Mammoth is a action, comedy, science fiction film directed by Abram Cox.
On a hot summer afternoon in the sleepy town of Blackwater Louisiana, a meteor streaks
across the sky and crashes through the roof of the local Natural History Museum.
The meteor is actually a spaceship containing an alien life form which animates
the museum's partially frozen Woolly Mammoth and begins a rampage.
Local authorities and Government Investigators join forces with Frank Abernathy, the Museum Curator, and his
father Simon, a B-Movie enthusiast, to bring down the giant mammoth in this alien-invasion flick!
Dr. Frank Abernathy, played by Vincent Ventresca.
Jack Abernathy, played by Summer Glau.
Simon Abernathy, played by Tom Skerritt.
Gordon, played by Constantin Drăgănescu.
Squirrelly, played by Cole Williams.
Sheriff Marion Morrison, played by Charles Carroll.
Mammoth is a 2006 American science fiction comedy horror television film
directed, co-written, and co-executive produced by Tim Cox.
The film stars Vincent Ventresca, Summer Glau, Leila
Arcieri, Cole Williams, and Tom Skerritt.
The film explores themes of mammoth, museum, alien life-form.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.